const CSR = [
	{
		questionText: 'CSR starts with',
		ans: ['A.245'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'A.245',
		ans: ['Extent of laws made by Parliament and by the legislatures of states'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'A.246',
		ans: ['Subject-matter of laws made by Parliament and by the legislatures of states'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'A.248',
		ans: ['Parliament has exclisve powers to make laws with respect to Residuary powers'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'A.249',
		ans: ['RS can pass resolution to make law on state list by the parliament national interest '],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'A.250',
		ans: ['Power of Parliament to legislate with respect to any matter in the state list if a Proclamation of Emergency is in operation '],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'A.252',
		ans: ['Power of Parliament to legislate for two or more states by consent and adoption of such legislation by any other state '],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'A.253',
		ans: ['To implement international treaty parliament can make laws on statelist without consent'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'A.251',
		ans: ['Inconsistency between laws made by Parliament under articles 249 and 250 and laws made by the legislatures of states, then union law is considered married'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'A.254',
		ans: ['Inconsistency between laws made by Parliament and laws made by the legislatures of states'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'A.256',
		ans: ['The executive powers of every state shall be so excercised as to ensure compliance with the lasws made by the parlimanent'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'A.257',
		ans: ['Control of the union over state certain cases'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'A.258',
		ans: ['Poer of the state to confer power etc.. on state in certain cases'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'A.261',
		ans: ['full faith of credibility'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'A.262',
		ans: ['Inter state water dispute, by parliament'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'A.263',
		ans: ['Inter state dispute other than water, by president'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'A.275',
		ans: ['Satutary grants'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'A.282',
		ans: ['Discretionary Grants'],
	},
];

export default CSR;
